beautyschoolsdirectory.com 2014-11-22

# Terms of Use / Privacy Statement | Beauty Schools Directory

Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity. It is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you provide and to help you in making informed decisions when using our site, products and services. This Privacy Policy will be continually assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers’ needs.

Access to and use of this web site is available only to United States residents who can form legally binding contracts under applicable law. If you do not qualify, you may not use the web site. In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, no one under 13 years of age can use the web site. If you are a minor between the ages of 13 and 18, you may use the site only in conjunction with your parent, legal guardian or other responsible adult.

As described below, some of your personally identifiable information will be used by us for the purpose of contacting you regarding the information that you have requested. By using the web site, you expressly consent to our use of your personal information and also to the disclosure to and use of this information in our efforts contact you and for continued marketing effort by the schools listed on our site charged with communicating with our customers and potential customers. Your acknowledge that communications to, from and through this web site are not confidential. You agree that by submitting communications through this web site, no confidential, fiduciary, contractually implied or other relationship is created between you and this web site other than pursuant to this Privacy Policy. 

In addition, we work with FetchBack to display Retargeted ads to our site prospects, on our behalf, across the Internet. They collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information about your visits to our Website, and your interaction with our products and services. The anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. No Personally Identifiable Information is collected during this process. To read FetchBack's Privacy Policy, [click here](http://www.fetchback.com/privacy.html "FetchBack Privacy Policy"). If you do not want FetchBack to collect this information, you may opt our of their service. Opting out will not in any way affect your use of our site. To Opt-Out of Fetchback Retargeting, please [click here](http://www.fetchback.com/optout.html "FetchBack Opt Out"). Visit the Network Advertising Initiatives Opt-Out by [clicking here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp "Network Advertising Initiatives Opt-Out").

 **What information do we collect?  
** We collect personally identifiable information you voluntarily choose to disclose and aggregate information that is automatically collected when you visit the web site.  
Personally identifiable information refers to information that tells us specifically who you are and is collected when you choose to request information from the schools listed on our site. This information can include your name, address, phone number, current email address, programs of interest and other information you choose to provide. If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain your email address and messages together with our responses.

Like many websites, we use “cookies”.  Cookies are small programs that we transfer to your hard drive that allow us to recognize you and to pass information about your website visit to different portions of this web site. If you do not want us to use cookies, you can easily disable them by going to the toolbar of your web browser, and clicking on the “help” button. Follow the instructions that will prevent the browser from accepting cookies, or set the browser to inform you when you receive a new cookie. In addition, you may visit this and other websites anonymously through the use of utilities provided by other private companies.

Aggregate information is automatically provided by your computer and cannot be tied back to you as a specific individual. Examples include:  
• referral data (the web sites you visited just before and just after the web site)  
• date and time of your visits  
• pages viewed and time spent at the web site  
• browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Macintosh platform)  
• Internet Protocol (IP) address. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer on the Internet.

 **How do we use the personal information that you provide to us?**  
Your personal information is used to match your interests with the beauty schools that provide the services you seek. We collect information you provide to us when you begin the process to request information from schools through BeautySchoolsDirectory.com, even if you do not click the "Submit," "Request Information" or "Apply" buttons, as well as when you do submit a form through our website. We may also store your information for the purpose of communicating with you about the programs and services offered by the schools listed on our site and send you updates if and when they become available. We also use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service, and making other products and services available to our customers and prospective customers. 

**Sharing information with third parties**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

We may share your information with third party service providers. We cannot and do not make any representations about the practices and policies of these companies, and they are not subject to our Privacy Policy.

 **How do we protect your information?  
** We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect. This software provides a limited degree of protection against unauthorized access or disclosure, as well as accidental loss, alteration or destruction.

 **Do we comply with legally compelled disclosure of information?  
** We may release any private information about you that we possess when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; to enforce or apply our Privacy Policy and/or other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of us, the site users or others.  
What about other sites linked to this one?

Please be aware that once you leave the site and enter another web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by these sites, nor the information or content contained therein. Please read over the rules and policies of these sites before proceeding.

**Beauty Schools Directory Scholarship Privacy Policy**  
If BeautySchoolsDirectory.com users choose to apply for one of the Beauty Schools Marketing Group scholarship drawings, it is asked that they provide their contact information (name, address, email address, etc.) and academic interests and measurements (programs of interest, schools of interest, GPA, SAT, etc.). Information is voluntarily submitted by the user via a secure scholarship application form. Beauty Schools Marketing Group may share this information with selected institutions of higher education and other educational organizations. After submitting a scholarship entry, if BeautySchoolsDirectory.com users ‘opt-in’, they will become part of our e-newsletter database and subsequently receive e-newsletters. If BeautySchoolsDirectory.com users choose to ‘opt-in’ for a third party offer on our form, personal information may be sent to third parties that are not affiliated with us under common ownership. These third party entities may be interested in marketing products or services to such users or in asking them questions, both online and offline.

**Copyrighted Material  
** The integrity of our web content is important to us. We have taken measures to make sure all web content on our site is original and owned by us or provided with consent by our clients, advertisers, and other contributors. If you believe we have misattributed any content or are infringing on your copyrighted content, please contact us at [info@beautyschoolsdirectory.com](mailto:info@beautyschoolsdirectory.com). We vigorously monitor the web for unauthorized use of our original content and design work, and reserve the right to pursue all available legal remedies to enforce our intellectual property rights.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
** Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Contact Us  
** If you would like to learn more about our privacy policy, or to access your personally identifiable information contained on our website, you may contact us at:

Beauty Schools Marketing Group  
15500 W. 113th Street, Suite #200  
Lenexa, KS 66219  
By e-mail: [info@beautyschoolsdirectory.com  
](mailto:info@beautyschoolsdirectory.com)By phone: 913-254-6000 

You will be required to provide identification information to assure that this information is not released to others. We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time without prior notification.
